<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What we are vs. What we are not on National Athletics League</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What we are vs. What we are not on National Athletics League</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s in it for you?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/athletes/</guid>
      <description>A real team! (And everything that goes with it)  Accountability on the tough days. Support on the rough days. Celebrations and appreciation on the good days. Hang out with other people who actually get what you&amp;rsquo;re doing. Eventually, things like gear, coaching, etc.  Team Competition  Wear your colors. Compete as a team. Go for the win as a team. Represent your community, town or city&amp;hellip; as a team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s in it for you?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/coaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/coaches/</guid>
      <description>This is already your job. build it. Successful and popular clubs will draw more people to take up athletics, either through the clubs, schools or with individual coaches.
Scholastic coaches Anything that drives demand for jumping, throwing and running ensures the athletics director and administration keep your T&amp;amp;F teams funded.
Independent coaches The more people who want to throw, jump and run, the more people who will be visiting your websites, your YouTube pages, finding you on CoachUp and calling you to schedule sessions (those that don’t join the clubs, that is!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>